{
    "id": "3957a313bec340159082b0bc38e8bec2",
    "title": "So, Very, Too",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "56cbc3a3571e4d2d86bf9304ddaf983d",
            "title": "So, Too And Very",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The room was ………………………….. hot that I could not sleep at all.",
                    "description": "We cannot use too or very before a that-clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ……………………………. polite a person to refuse.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern too..to. We can also express this idea using so. She is so polite that she cannot refuse.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The trains are …………………………. crowded.",
                    "description": "Either could be used to talk about extremes.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "very",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There were far …………………………….. many applicants for the job.",
                    "description": "The expression too many can be modified by far.",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "so",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was …………………………. upset that she did not talk to anybody.",
                    "description": "Only so is possible before a that-clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The water is …………………………… salty that we cannot drink it.",
                    "description": "Only so is possible before a that-clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have always been ……………………………. kind to me.",
                    "description": "We cannot use too much before an adjective without a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We arrived ……………………………… late to have dinner.",
                    "description": "We cannot use too much before an adjective without a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "very much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a …………………………… intelligent child.",
                    "description": "We cannot use so before adjective + noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "so",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We shall be …………………………. pleased if you can spend a few days with us.",
                    "description": "The expression only too can mean very.",
                    "answers": [
                        "only too",
                        "very",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ask …………………………………… too many questions.",
                    "description": "We can use far to modify too many. Much is not used before too many.",
                    "answers": [
                        "far",
                        "much",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We got ……………………………… answers to our advertisement.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so many",
                        "too many",
                        "very many",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}